<document>
  <properties>
    <title>RPGUnit Issues</title>
    <author email="lacton@users.sourceforge.net">lacton</author>
  </properties>
  <body>
    <release version="0.3" date="SVN" description="Version 0.3 Release Notes">
      <action dev="lacton" type="add">
        Added online help for commands RUCRTTST and RUCALLTST.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        Changed PGM parameter for RUCRTTST command to TSTPGM, to be consistent with RUCALLTST command.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        Fixed RUCALLTST completion message so that the words are suffixed by 's' only if there are several of them.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        Fixed fail() so that calling it from inside a monitor block actually raises an exception outside the monitor block. Until then, calling fail() from inside a monitor block would only force a jump to the on-error part of the block.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        If the setUpSuite procedure raises an error, RUCALLTST command tries to execute the tearDownSuite procedure anyway before ending. That way, the clean-up activities in tearDownSuite get a chance to run.
	Also, an error during setUpSuite is no longer a special case. It is simply reported in the spool file, like any error raised during a test run. Same for tearDownSuite.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        RUCALLTST command generates spool files with more helpful names than QSYSPRT. The spool file name is RPGUNIT and its associated user data is the name of the test program.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="add">
        RUCALLTST command sends status messages during test execution.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="add">
        RUCRTTST command gives a completion message when it ends successfully.
      </action>
      <action dev="lacton" type="fix">
        Fixed RPGUnit's acceptance tests so that they pass when submitted from a server job (e.g., using RMTCMD).
      </action>	      
    </release>
    <release version="0.2" date="2006-09-05" description="Version 0.2 Release Notes">
      <action dev="lacton" type="add">
        Uploaded source code to sourceforge.
      </action>
    </release>
  </body>
</document>
